selena-fan.com 2013-09-07

# BuddyTV Privacy Policy

**BUDDYTV  
PRIVACY POLICY**

BuddyTV ("BuddyTV") is committed to protecting its users' privacy. This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy"), as set forth below, covers [buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/) (“[buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/),” the “Site,” or the "website") and applies solely to information collected on [buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/) . Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we will treat personally and non-personally identifiable information we collect on [buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/). This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.    

**What personally identifiable information is collected from me?**    

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to the Site. Except with respect to certain designated elements of the Site that require registration, you can use [buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/) without divulging any personally identifiable information, including your email address. The Site does not collect personally identifiable information about you unless you expressly provide such information to us on a voluntary basis. For example, you may provide your personally identifiable information to complete contest entry forms, to complete your registration on the Site or the various services offered on the Site, including community postings such as the [buddytv.com](http://buddytv.com/) Community, chats and bulletin boards. Except as described below, in those instances in which you "opt-in" to receive offers directly from our third party partners, such personally identifiable information will never be shared with third parties outside of BuddyTV and its affiliated companies or third party vendors acting on their behalf.  

We may, from time to time, give you the opportunity to receive special offers, such as newsletters, email reminders or special discounts, directly from companies with which we partner. In order to take advantage of these opportunities, you must affirmatively authorize us to share your personally identifiable information with these third party partners; we will never share such information unless you specifically "opt-in" to receive such an offer from one of our partners. Similarly, as part of certain sweepstakes entries we may also give you the opportunity to sign up to receive special offers from our advertising partners. Again, during the entry process, your information will be shared with our partners only if you take specific action to indicate that you would like us to do so.  

You may choose to provide us with the certain personally identifiable information when using the Site or the various services offered on the Site, including: 

    * Your name  
    * Your home contact information (physical address and/or phone number)  
    * Online contact information (email address)  
    * Your login information  

In addition, at times, we may ask you to provide non-personally identifiable information about yourself that may be linked with your personally identifiable information you provide. Provision of this information is optional. Such information includes: 

    * Gender  
    * Preferences (what you like or dislike)  
    * Survey answers (votes and ratings of TV shows)    

**What non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically?**    

We automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information from you to optimize our web pages for your computer such as 

    * clickstream information (internet protocol ("IP") address, internet service provider, platform type,   
      date/time stamp) http protocol information (last URL requested and browser type)  
    * interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image)  
    * computer information (computer and browser information)  
    * search terms (search text)  

We may use such non-personally identifiable information for internal purposes, including, but not limited to, improving the content of the Site and the services offered on the Site. (See "How is my information used?") 

**How is my information used?**    

We will use personally identifiable information that you submit to the Site for the purposes for which you submitted it. At the time you provide personally identifiable information, you have the option of instructing us not to send you our special email offers, and of affirmatively consenting to receiving email offers about, or from, our partners.  

We may disclose personally identifiable information when required by law or when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, court order, government investigation or legal process.  We may, in our sole discretion, comply with subpoenas seeking personal information without notifying you. 

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Site to enhance the Site and our product offerings, to maintain and secure the Site, and to understand the interests of Site visitors. Generally, we use non-personally identifiable information to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather information for aggregate use (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information). 

We may also use the statistical compilation and aggregation of non-personally identifiable information and may provide such information to third parties for marketing, advertising or research purposes. 

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with a merger or consolidation with such third party or the sale of some or all of our assets, provided that such third party agrees to comply with the then-current version of this Privacy Policy.   

**How is my information kept secure?**    

We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our Sites, and we periodically review and update security measures in light of current technologies.  However, you should be aware that security measures sometimes fail, and we make no guarantees regarding the security of your personally identifiable information.   

**Profile Preferences**    

You may change your personal profile preferences on the site at any time.   

**Email Policies**    

By default, we send a weekly and sometimes bi-weekly newsletter updates regarding TV news stories, new features, and updates from BuddyTV.  We also send a variety of notification emails pertaining to your profile and your friends interactions with the site.  You have full control over which emails you wish to receive, simply go to “My Profile” and edit your preferences.   

**Inviting Friends**    

BuddyTV is more fun with friends!  The site is a community site made up of friendly TV lovers and is intended to be shared with friends; however, it is completely optional to invite friends.   

When inviting friends, we will send an email to the addresses you enter indicating it is a message from you so that they know it is coming from you.  If a friend does not respond, we may send one or two reminder messages on your behalf.   

As an added convenience, BuddyTV offers the ability import address books from Hotmail, Yahoo, Gmail, and AOL.  We access the address book only once for the sole purpose of retrieving your friends’ information so that you can select who you would like to invite.  We do not store any login details or use them for any other purpose than to retrieve your contacts.  We never invite contacts that you do not explicitly select and no emails will be sent to your friends other than the invite email unless they register to join BuddyTV.  By selecting such contacts, you consent to our access of your email in-box and contact list for this purpose, and waive any federal, state, or local law which restricts access to your in-box or email communications.   

**What are cookies and how are they used by the Sites?**    

Cookies are files that a web site places on an individual's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most web sites, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. 

Our cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. We will not share or sell non-aggregated information contained within cookies with any third party. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature, but you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with such special features as customized content delivery. Cookies can be removed from your computer by following Internet browser "help" file directions. 

**What do I need to know about third party sites, co-branded sites, and BuddyTV's online business partners?**    

We have established relationships that allow visitors to the Site to go directly to sites operated by third parties. Some of these sites may be co-branded with our logos; however, they are not operated or maintained by BuddyTV. We are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the Site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute our sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you have left the Site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. 

We may use third parties to manage sweepstakes, games, contests, chats or other features, and these parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. 

**BigDoor Virtual Economy Platform**    

We have incorporated in the Website loyalty programs and other offers provided through BigDoor Media.  Your use of the BigDoor Virtual Economy Platform (“VEP”) is governed by the terms of use posted at [www.bigdoor.com/veptermsofuse](http://www.bigdoor.com/veptermsofuse) and privacy policy posted at [_http://www.bigdoor.com/privacy/_](http://www.bigdoor.com/privacy/) (collectively “VEP Terms”) which may include provisions regarding use and disclosure of your personal information. The VEP program allows you to participate in a virtual economy consisting of virtual currency/points, awards, levels and virtual goods (“VEP Components”). By interacting with VEP Components on the Site or otherwise using the VEP program you agree to be bound by the VEP Terms, including VEP’s privacy policy, which may differ from our policy and terms. The VEP Terms contain a dispute resolution provision that you must read carefully and agree to before using the service. The VEP service is not available where prohibited by law and is not available for use if you are under the age of 13.   

**Does BuddyTV use Third Party Ad Servers?**    

We use third party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the Site. These companies may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you would like more information about this practice please visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).   

**Does BuddyTV collect personally identifiable information from children?**    

We ask that all parents spend time with their children and monitor what sites their children are visiting. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We also suggest that no children under 18 submit personally identifiable information to any game, membership, contest or promotion that we might host without first obtaining a parent's consent. Our Site is not intended for use by and is not directed to children.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**    

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Site.   

**Contact Information**    

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

BuddyTV Customer Service   
190 Queen Anne Ave. Suite 250  
Seattle, WA 98109  
USA  

E-mail: [privacy@buddytv.com](mailto:privacy@buddytv.com)

Last Updated on February 2, 2010
